6% stronger.  It is seen trading above 1960 65.  Let's take an
opinion on this also.  Actually, this result of today's Stock of the Day
recommendation has been a
part of the review recommendation.  But let's take a slightly
longer perspective on this from Amrish Sir.
Amrish Sir, what is your opinion on ICI or Labad
Sir?
Look,
I am positive on both general insurance and life insurance in the insurance space
and the way GST cuts have
come.  I think the next one for like health
insurance has been quite positive.  So
something like ah ICICI Lombard I think the
upside here could be around 2300 2400.
We have created a strong presence in the capital market space